One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The end of the dream, the end of the sea
‫منتهى غايتي، منتهى البحار‬
We all have different places we want to go
‫لكل امرؤ وجهة يتولاها‬
But to start we've got to show what we're made of
‫لولا بصيص واحد يبقى‬
We'll be legends, we're gonna take the world by storm
‫ما إن تكشف الأسطورة عن صفحاتها‬
Sparks are flying, NO LIMITS! This is where it starts
‫حماسة متأججة بلا حدود، هلم جرا إلى‬
ONE PIECE!!
‫ون بيس!‬
ALL OF US, I've got a question for you
‫كل واحد منا، لدي سؤال لكم:‬
Have you let the world and all its burdens bring your dreams down?
‫أما زال درب أحلامكم سالكًا؟‬
Every cell in me is getting restless - They're about to blow, oh, it's just too much Every cell in me is getting restless - They're about to blow, oh, it's just too much
‫خلاياي الهامدة تُثار وتفيض حماسةً‬
Still we try, ALL OF US have our own paths we cling to
‫إنما كل واحدٍ منا في مغامرة‬
ALL OF US, I've got something to tell you
‫كل واحد منا، لدي ما أخبركم به‬
ALL OF US, I've got something to tell you If you've got a dream that's worth a damn you've gotta stand tall
‫كل واحد منا، لدي ما أخبركم به ما من معركةٍ نخوضها إلا تحمل العبرة‬
If you've got a dream that's worth a damn you've gotta stand tall
‫ما من معركةٍ نخوضها إلا تحمل العبرة‬
Random clues suddenly fit together
‫وما خُفي في السياق المُتناثر يحمل معنى مترابط‬
Threads of time weaving into an intricate tapestry
‫وخيوط الزمان ستُحاك تارةً أخرى‬
We can't stop the world from turning, it's changing along with every one of-
‫وبنا جميعًا سيتبدل حال العالم على الدوام‬
Admiral Kizaru has made landfall!
‫الأميرال كيزارو اخترق صفوف العدو‬
The enemy has mobilized!
‫ترقبوا تحركات العدو‬
Don't let them fire those lasers!
‫لا تدعوهم يطلقوا الليزر‬
Attack!
‫أطلقوا‬
– It's a weaponized sea beast!
‫إنها وحوش البحر المسلحة‬
Sentomaru
‫سينتومارو‬
The weaponized sea beasts are attacking!
‫وحوش البحر المسلحة يأتونا تواليًا‬
We're in trouble!
‫يا للمصيبة‬
We've gotta take them down before they sink us!
‫فلنبادرهم قبل أن يهاجمونا‬
Leave it to me!
‫أنا لها‬
Steam Knuckle!
‫بُرجمة البخار‬
Forget the ships!
‫انسوا أمر السفن‬
You're dealing with me!
‫فإني لكم بالمرصاد‬
The vice admirals have landed, too!
‫نواب الأميرالات هبطوا الجزيرة‬
Which lab are they holding the Cipher Pol agents in?!
‫أين المختبر المحتجز داخله عملاء السايفر بول؟‬
The one up there.
‫هناك‬
In the Labophase...
‫في المختبر...‬
The Marines and the robot sea beasts...
‫البحرية والوحوش الآلية‬
just started fighting at the shore!
‫اندلع بينهم قتال على الساحل‬
As long as Sentomaru is commanding the pacifista,
‫ما دام سينتومارو يقود الباشيفيستا،‬
Pacifista Authority Hierarchy Five Elders Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites) Authority Chip
‫تسلسل السيطرة‬ ‫على الباشيفيستا‬ ‫الشيوخ الخمسة‬ ‫فيغابانك‬ ‫(ستيلا والأقمار)‬ ‫شريحة السلطة‬
Sentomaru Authority Chip
‫شريحة السلطة سينتومارو‬
Sentomaru
‫سينتومارو‬
Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites) Pacifista Authority Hierarchy Vegapunk (Stella + Satellites) Authority Chip
‫تسلسل السيطرة‬ ‫على الباشيفيستا فيغابانك‬ ‫(ستيلا والأقمار)‬ ‫شريحة السلطة فيغابانك‬
Five Elders Pacifista Authority Hierarchy
‫تسلسل السيطرة‬ ‫على الباشيفيستا الشيوخ الخمسة‬
the island's defenses are impenetrable!
‫يُفترض أن دفاع الجزيرة منيع‬
Isn't that why he showed up?! To take out Sentomaru?!
‫أتظنون أنه أتى للتخلص من سينتومارو؟‬
Kizaru?!
‫كيزارو؟‬
He's here already?!
‫هل وصل؟‬
No way!
‫غير معقول‬
He's fighting right below us as we speak!
‫إنهم يتقاتلون في الأسفل الآن‬
Kizaru, huh?
‫كيزارو إذًا؟‬
This brings back some unpleasant memories from Sabaody Archipelago...
‫رؤيته تقلّب مواجع ما حدث في أرخبيل شابوندي‬
Too bad. You guys are toast.
‫لن تلبثوا أن تموتوا‬
No way! Fighting Kizaru, of all people...
‫لا يُعقل، أما غير كيزارو يقاتله؟‬
I'm sorry, Sentomaru!
‫سامحني يا سينتومارو‬
What a heartbreaking battle!
‫بئس الذريعة التي تجبرك على قتاله، لن ألومك إن فررت‬
Keep your chin up, Stella!
‫روح عن نفسك يا ستيلا‬
For now, just focus on cracking the passcode!
‫صب اهتمامك على كشف رمز المرور في الوقت الراهن‬
Edison is right!
‫إديسون محق، فلنعجل‬
Okay!
‫أصبتما‬
Just surrender!
‫يستحسن أن تستسلم...‬
Sentomaru!
‫يا سينتومارو-كن!‬
Sacred Yasakani Jewel.
‫جوهرة الفاصلة المقدسة‬
I'm sorry, Unc!
‫اعذرني يا عم‬
Straw Hat Luffy and I made a promise!
‫لكني قطعت وعدًا لقبعة القش‬
Straw Hat?
‫قبعة القش؟‬
Since when do you side with pirates?
‫متى صرت توالي القراصنة؟‬
I'll work with anyone...
‫سأتعاون مع أي أحد...‬
who helps the man that saved my life escape this island!
‫إن كان يعين منقذ حياتي على الهرب من الجزيرة‬
How odd.
‫عجيب‬
They asked us to hunt bears, but...
‫ألم نُكلف نحن بصيد الدببة؟‬
Did that child beat us to it?
‫هل هزمهم الصبي؟‬
I hate the weaklings that live in the village!
‫أهل قريتي ضعفاء فلم أحتملهم‬
I'm never going back!
‫لن أرجع إليهم ثانيةً‬
They kicked you out, huh?
‫هل نفوك؟‬
I'm so tough, I don't even get hungry!
‫أنا قوي فلا يقرصني الجوع‬
But I wanna work!
‫لكني أريد عملًا‬
I want money!
‫فإني أحتاج المال‬
Oh, you have something you'd like to buy?
‫أمن شيءٍ تريد شرائه؟‬
Rice balls!
‫كرات الأرز‬
You were such a cute kid...
‫كم كنتَ لطيفًا‬
Work?
‫عمل؟‬
You seem pretty confident in your physical strength.
‫باديةٌ عليك ثقتك بقوتك البدنية‬
Say, kid, how would you like to be my bodyguard?
‫أتريد أن تكون حارسي الشخصي يا فتى؟‬
Are you gonna hire me?!
‫هل تقدم لي عملًا؟‬
I'll do it!
‫أقبله‬
Unc! Unc!
‫يا عم، يا عم‬
You mean me?
‫أتعنيني؟‬
Unc!
‫يا عم‬
How should I protect Old Man Punk?
‫كيف ليَ أن أحمي العجوز بانك؟‬
Unc?
‫أقلت «عم»؟‬
Do I look old enough to be an uncle?
‫ما زلت في ريعان شبابي‬
I want you to teach me, Unc!
‫علِّمني يا عم‬
I did my best to teach you, Sentomaru.
‫بذلت كل جهدي في تعليمك يا سينتومارو-كن‬
Ashigara Dokkoi!
‫الوهز بالثقل‬
But...
‫لذا،‬
my defense...
‫فإن دفاعي...‬
is as strong as yours.
‫لن يخسر أمامك...‬
Pacifista.
‫أيها الباشيفيستا‬
Your commander is unconscious, so there will be a change of plans.
‫من كان له الأولوية عليكم فقد وعيه وتغيرت الخطة‬
Assist the Marine ships against the weaponized sea beasts.
‫تعاونوا مع سفن البحرية لإغراق وحوش البحر المسلحة‬
The pacifista's directive...
‫تنسيق الباشيفيستا...‬
has been overwritten.
‫تغير‬
Such a waste to sink them,
‫إغراقهم تبديد لمواردنا‬
but if we can keep only one, we choose the pacifista.
‫ولكن الأفضل لنا اختيار الباشيفيستا عليهم‬
Give me a full damage report...
‫ما الأضرار بالدقائق القليلة الماضية؟‬
of the last few minutes.
‫أبلغها لي‬
Yes, sir!
‫عُلم‬
Sentomaru is down!
‫هُزم سينتومارو‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Let's hurry and deactivate the defense system!
‫علينا التعجل بتعطيل النظام الدفاعي‬
Yeah!
‫أجل‬
We can't let Sentomaru's sacrifice be in vain!
‫إياكما أن تهدرا الوقت الذي وفره لنا سينتومارو‬
Forget it. I'm Vegapunk, too!
‫لا جدوى فيما تفعلون، فأنا أيضًا فيغابانك‬
Kizaru is light itself!
‫إن كيزارو الضوء ذاته‬
He can pass through the laser barrier!
‫يمكنه تجاوز حاجز الليزر‬
You mean he can just come right in?!
‫أتعني أنه يقدر على الدخول إلى هنا؟‬
Yes!
‫أجل‬
He totally wiped the floor with us once already!
‫أذلّنَا ذلًا قبل زمن‬
It's been a while...
‫مر وقت طويل‬
Straw Hat crew.
‫يا طاقم قبعة القش‬
Hurry up, hurry up!
‫أسرعوا أسرعوا‬
As soon as the barrier is down, we're outta here!
‫سنهرب حالما يُعطل الحاجز‬
So far, so good!
‫الأمور تجري بسلاسة‬
I'll just take the ship around back!
‫سأحمل السفينة إلى الخلف‬
Sounds good!
‫نعتمد عليكِ‬
Let's eat while we can.
‫فلنأكل قدر الإمكان‬
Yeah.
‫أجل‬
You can't fight on an empty stomach.
‫المرء لا يقاتل على معدة خاوية‬
You're eating now, of all times?
‫ما لكما تأكلان؟‬
We're gonna escape soon, guys!
‫نحن بصدد الهروب من هنا‬
Lilith! What's up with that?!
‫ما هذا يا ليليث؟‬
An emergency alarm?!
‫إنذار الطوارئ؟‬
Why?! I thought this place...
‫لماذا؟‬
was impenetrable!
‫حصينًا؟...‬
At any cost, protect:
‫الأولوية في الحماية:‬
The power plant.
‫محطة الطاقة‬
Punk Records.
‫سجلات بانك‬
York.
‫يورك‬
And ideally...
‫وإن كانت لي الخيرة لحميت صاحبًا قديمًا‬
but alas...
‫ولكن للأسف...‬
At any cost, eliminate:
‫الإبادة لازمة لما يلي:‬
Dr. Vegapunk.
‫الدكتور فيغابانك‬
Kizaru made it inside the dome!
‫كيزارو اقتحم القبة‬
Luffy and the others are out there!
‫ولوفي والآخرين بالخارج‬
That can't be good. Luffy!
‫ورطة عويصة، لوفي-سان!‬
Tell them through the snail!
‫أبلغهم بحلزون الاتصال حالًا‬
Luffy! Run!
‫اهربوا يا لوفي‬
Until the ship is in place,
‫لن يُعطل الحاجز حتى ننتهي من نقل السفينة‬
Stussy!
‫ستوسي‬
Stussy?!
‫ستوسي-تشان!‬
Nami, I'm borrowing this!
‫سأستعيره يا نامي-سان‬
Sheesh! What gives?!
‫تبًّا، ما هذا؟ مسدس فقاعات؟‬
Looks like he forgot about you!
‫يبدو أن صاحبك تخلى عنك‬
So you got backup and thought you could make your move?!
‫هل اغتررت بنفسك لأن حليفك جاء؟‬
Between Kizaru and me,
‫بوجودي أنا وكيزارو‬
all of you are dead!
‫ستهلكون جميعًا‬
Don't underestimate us!
‫لا تستخفنا!‬
No wonder their ship wasn't at the shore.
‫لهذا لم أجد سفينتهم عند الساحل‬
It was here all along!
‫فقد كانت بالأعلى هنا‬
Hurry up!
‫بسرعة‬
Kizaru?! He's a Marine admiral!
‫كيزارو!‬
What's the plan, Luffy?!
‫ما العمل يا لوفي؟‬
Where'd he go?!
‫أين ذهب؟‬
Hey, Luffy!
‫يا لوفي‬
Hey, long time no–
‫أهلًا، طالت الغيـ...‬
That's just bad manners.
‫يا لسوء آدابك‬
Kizaru!
‫كيزارو‬
Compared to two years ago...
‫نحن أقوى بمئة مرة...‬
we're a hundred times stronger!
‫مما كنا عليه قبل عامين!‬
The Previous Day Mary Geoise
‫اليوم السابق‬ ‫بماريجوا‬
He's finally reached the top!
‫أفلح في تسلقه أخيرًا‬
Invincible Slave Kuma has returned!
‫العبد المنيع كوما عاد‬
Soldiers, stop him!
‫أوقفوه حالًا أيها الجنود‬
What's he doing here?!
‫ما الذي يخطط إليه؟‬
Oh no!
‫هذا تعيس‬
We can't stop him!
‫لا نقدر عليه‬
Ursus Shock!
‫صدمة الدب‬
Such an insolent slave...
‫ما أنت إلا عبد‬
What do you think you're doing?
‫ما الذي تفعله؟‬
The other day it was the Revolutionary Army, and now this...
‫هاجمنا الجيش الثوري سابقًا والآن أنت‬
This destruction is unprecedented, Kuma!
‫لم يسبق لهذا الدمار مثيلًا قط يا كوما‬
F-Fleet Admiral Sakazuki...
‫المشير ساكازوكي‬
Worthless scum!
‫لا فائدة تُرجى منكم‬
You soldiers are completely useless!
‫إنكم لجنودٍ متقاعسين‬
Hey, Akainu!
‫يا أكاينو‬
I ordered lobster for dinner last night, but they said they were all out!
‫أمرتهم أن يعدوا الروبيان في عشاء البارحة لكنه لم يكن متوفرًا‬
That's never happened before!
‫لم يحدث هذا من قبل‬
What's happening to Mary Geoise's food supply?!
‫ماذا حل بمؤونة ماريجوا؟‬
Hey, that's not important right now!
‫هذا ليس وقت التشكي‬
I've just been injured!
‫فأنا مصاب‬
Kuma the Tyrant is a mere slave!
‫ما الطاغية كوما إلا عبدٌ الآن فأعدمه من فورك‬
The thing is, Kuma...
‫اسمع يا كوما‬
if we can't control you,
‫إذا لم تكن تحت طوعنا،‬
then we can't afford to have you on the loose.
‫فلن نترك شخصًا خطر مثلك حرًّا طليقًا‬
Your sense of self should have been erased.
‫يُفترض أن وعيك تلاشى‬
You're as good as dead already.
‫حالك حال الجثة الهامدة...‬
So where do you think you're going?!
‫فأين تخال نفسك ذاهبًا؟‬
Hellhound
‫كلب الجحيم‬
I didn't know you still bled like a man.
‫لم أعلم أنك ما زلت تنزف كالبشر‬
Hold it, Kuma!
‫مهلًا يا كوما‬
Bark all you want, but Kuma will never regain his sense of self.
‫مهما بكيتِ فلن يعود وعي كوما‬
He volunteered to be reborn as a weapon.
‫فقد تطوع بنفسه ليتحول إلى سلاح حربي‬
That's a lie!
‫كاذب‬
There's no way...
‫تطوعه بنفسه...‬
There's no way he chose that!
‫تطوعه بنفسه أمرٌ محال‬
He would never leave me behind!
‫فما كان ليتخلى عني‬
Hey! Where is Kuma?!
‫أين كوما؟‬
Don't tell me you let him get away!
‫أيعقل أنه أفلت منك؟‬
You're the fleet admiral!
‫وهذا وأنت المشير!‬
Where are you going?
‫أين عساه يذهب؟‬
You're just a puppet...
‫وهو مجرد دمية...‬
Present Day Egghead New World
‫اليوم الحاضر‬ ‫بإيغهيد‬ ‫بالعالم الجديد‬
without a mind or free will...
‫لا وعي ولا إرادة له!‬
Pacifista and all Marines, keep shooting!
‫واصلوا إطلاق النار يا جنود والبحرية وأيها الباشيفيستا‬
Destroy the weaponized sea beasts!
‫دمروا وحوش البحر المسلحة‬
Enter the Fabriophase! Occupy the island!
‫ادخلوا طابق المصنع واحتلوا الجزيرة‬
Admiral Kizaru has entered the Labophase above the clouds!
‫الأميرال كيزارو اقتحم طابق المختبر فوق الغيوم‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Black Mamba!
‫الثعابين السوداء‬
Now I see how you were able to defeat Kaido.
‫كما هو متوقع من الرجل الذي هزم كايدو!‬
You're quite the powerhouse.
‫لستَ خصمًا سهلًا!‬
However...
‫ولكن،‬
what would make a pirate like you want to protect Vegapunk?
‫لمَ يحاول قرصانٌ حماية فيغابانك؟‬
You tell me!
‫سؤالي من نفس المنطلق‬
Why do you guys wanna kill Apple Gramps?!
‫لماذا تحاولون قتل العجوز ذو التفاحة؟‬
It's not that I want to...
‫ما كان قتله رغبتي‬
How far is he going?!
‫إلى أي مدى سيطير؟‬
I don't want to kill him.
‫ما كان قتله رغبتي إطلاقًا‬
I've known Vegapunk for a long time...
‫عرفت فيغابانك منذ زمن طويل‬
so I'd appreciate it if you'd stay out of this.
‫لذا هلّا تكف عن اعتراض طريقي‬
Acceleration is power!
‫التسارع قوة‬
It's complete!
‫اكتمل‬
Its name is Vegaforce-01!
‫أسميته فيغافورس-1‬
The dream of man!
‫إنه حلم البشرية‬
A giant robot!
‫آلي عملاق‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
What's going on?!
‫ماذا يحدث؟‬
I thought I was a goner!
‫حسبتني هلكت‬
Oh... Oh no!
‫ويلي‬
Franky! Bonney!
‫فرانكي، بوني‬
Lilith?!
‫ليليث؟‬
Run!
‫اهربا‬
The Vegaforce-01 is gonna...
‫ففيغافورس-1....‬
Just run!
‫اهربا فحسب‬
Damn it all!
‫سحقًا‬
The robot of our dreams, the Vegaforce-01...
‫دمر آلي أحلامنا فيغافورس-1‬
That jackass is gonna pay!
‫تبًّا، هذا لا يُغتفر‬
Is the Sunny alright?!
‫هل الساني سالمة؟‬
Hey! Straw Hat flew right through us!
‫تمهل، قذف بقبعة القش بعيدًا أيضًا‬
Kizaru, you bastard!
‫أيها الوغد يا كيزارو‬
Look how big you've gotten, Bonney...
‫كبرتِ كثيرًا يا بوني‬
Kids these days grow up so fast.
‫أطفال هذه الأيام ينضجون سريعًا‬
Are you still carrying a grudge?
‫لا شك أنكِ تحملين حقدًا‬
An order was issued to assassinate the man you hate, Dr. Vegapunk.
‫لدي أوامر بقتل الدكتور فيغابانك الذي تحتقرينه‬
Shut up.
‫اخرس‬
I have a new target in my crosshairs!
‫تغير هدفي‬
Age Skewer!
‫الزمن القاتل‬
Whoa.
‫ويحي‬
I'd prefer...
‫لا تجبريني...‬
not to hurt any acquaintances outside the scope of my mission.
‫أن أمس معارفي بسوء ما لم أؤمر بذلك‬
No! Not that way...!
‫مهلًا، إن هذا الاتجاه...‬
Bonney!
‫بوني‬
That's it, Kizaru!
‫أيها الوغد كيزارو‬
Radical...
‫راديكال‬
Be–
‫بيـ...‬
Where'd he go?!
‫أين هو؟‬
He just vanished?!
‫أين اختفى؟‬
Stella's in danger!
‫ستيلا في خطر‬
Franky! Call them!
‫اتصل بهم يا فرانكي‬
Control Room Labophase
‫غرفة التحكم‬ ‫بالمختبر‬
Come in, control room!
‫أتسمعوني يا غرفة التحكم؟‬
Franky, are you okay?!
‫هل أنتم بخير يا فرانكي؟‬
We heard a big explosion over there!
‫سمعنا دوي انفجار ضخم من جهتكم توًّا‬
That you, Usopp? Is everyone alright?!
‫أهذا أنت يا أوسوب؟ هل الجميع بخير؟‬
What? Y-Yeah...
‫أ-أجل‬
Good to hear! So he's not there yet.
‫ارتحت، لم يصل بعد‬
What do you mean?
‫من تقصد؟‬
Eureka!
‫نجحنا‬
The deactivation code for the defense system...
‫رمز تعطيل نظام الدفاع...‬
– ...is cracked!
‫توصلنا إليه!‬
Really?!
‫حقًّا؟‬
In your face, York!
‫موتي بغيظك يا يورك‬
Dammit! You smart-asses!
‫تبًا لكم أيها العباقرة المزعجين‬
Franky, we can bring down the barrier at any time!
‫فرانكي-كن، باستطاعتنا تعطيل الحاجز متى أردنا‬
Did you move the Vegaforce-01 and the ship to the back?!
‫هل نقلتم السفينة بفيغافورس-1 إلى الخلف؟‬
No, because...
‫بشأن هذا...‬
What a pity.
‫للأسف الشديد‬
Your escape plan has failed.
‫باءت خطة هروبك بالفشل‬
Vegapunk.
‫يا فيغابانك‬
K-K-Kizaru!
‫كـ-كـ-كيزارو!‬
When did you get here?!
‫متى دخل إلى هنا؟‬
Wh... Wh-Wh-Wh-Why?!
‫لـ-لـ-لـ-لماذا؟‬
What happened to Luffy?!
‫ماذا حلّ بلوفي؟‬
We're done for...
‫انتهى أمرنا‬
So it was you who caused that explosion?
‫هل الانفجار الذي حدث توًّا من صنيعك؟‬
Yeah...
‫أجل‬
Unfortunately...
‫للأسف الشديد‬
your giant dream robot...
‫آلي الأحلام العملاق...‬
was blown to smithereens.
‫فجرته‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Hogwash!
‫غير معقول‬
I hope you understand...
‫تفهم أرجوك‬
This is very difficult for me, and I'd rather not draw it out.
‫هذه مهمة عسيرة علي فلا أريد إطالتها‬
What is it?!
‫ما الأمر؟‬
What?! What?!
‫ماذا يحدث؟‬
What is it this time?!
‫ما الأمر الآن؟‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Phew, that was spicy!
‫كان هذا ساخنًا‬
There you are.
‫ها هي ذي‬
So this must be...
‫أهذه...‬
Nice try knocking me all the way down!
‫أحسنت ركلي إلى الأسفل‬
I thought going through the barrier twice was gonna kill me for sure!
‫عبرتُ الحاجز مرتين، حسبتني هلكت!‬
Running so long lost track of just how long its been
‫ﺎﻨﻫ ﻰﻟﺇ ﻻﻮﺻﻭ ﺎﻬﺘﻌﻄﻗ ﺪﻗ ﺓﺮﻴﺴﻣ ﻱﺃ؟‬